[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
♪Even though my heart says I love you♪
♪Why am I like this?♪
♪I don't understand♪
♪What's wrong with my mouth and my heart?♪
♪Why won't they say the same thing?♪
♪Will we ever get to love each other?♪
If our project needs him, I will get him.
If I want you, how much do I have to pay?
Five hundred drinks. Tonight, Angel must be with me.
I never sold myself to anyone.
Keep your money and buy someone else.
I guess all the whores are hungry for money.
Are you planning meet up and fuck outside?
I'm waiting for the answer.
Hey!
I'm off work now. Not accepting any more clients.
You're still here?
Why did you keep me waiting for so long?
How are you going home when you're this drunk?
I can still stand up.
Give me your car key. I'll drive you home.
Where do you live?
There.
There? Where?
Hey.
Where is it?
With you, of course.
How can I take you to the right place?
We're almost there.
Stand still.
No.
Hey!
The scent is just so-so. Why so expensive?
So overpriced.
Why didn't you hold me up properly?
My ass hurts.
Ms. Peem!
Not now.
Stop!
Swallow it.
Hey!
Come on.
Go sit down and I'll get you a trash can.
Not now...
Vomit...
You don't need to give me anything
Because I don't want anything
Just let me...
...make my heart happy
Hey, Ms. Peem.
May I change your clothes?
Are you forcing yourself on me?
Your top is dirty.
I’ve brought a new one for you.
I’ll take this one off to wash it.
No, I can do it myself.
Come on, let me help you.
You're good at pleasing people.
That's why your clients love you, right?
And you're good in bed too, right?
With me, you acted like you'd never done it.
Ha. With others, I'm sure you're like a pro.
You think I'm rich, so you want my money?
I will spend money, money, and money on you.
Are you happy now?
Even though my heart says I love you
Why am I like this?
I don't understand
What's wrong with my mouth and my heart?
You're kinda cute when you're asleep.
Why won't they say the same thing?
Will we ever get to love each other?
Why does it have to be you?
Did the sound from my oven wake you?
Did you sleep well?
Here.
I saved one for you.
Is it good?
You haven't applied any lotion after showering.
Give me a sec.
Applying this will leave your skin feeling soft.
Your lips are tight, but your skin will be soft.
It'll be moisturized and glowing.
What did Techin talk to you about last night?
If you don't want to tell me, it's fine.
But if you come to work for me,
I'll pay you more than he'll pay you.
Ow!
Ow! Ow!
Stop!
Peem! I'm here to be your training partner, not to be beaten up by you.
You kept hitting me with your serves!
Jeez. Enough. It's my turn to serve.
Ow.
I'm hurting.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Ow!
Ow.
It hurts!
You're still alive?
This is the first time you failed to negotiate a deal.
I see you can still talk.
Huh?
Come on.
Stop rubbing it in.
Can't you see I'm already upset?
Seriously, do you need this person that badly?
Yes.
But normally, you're not this moody when there's a problem with your work.
It's not just about work, is it?
Get up and let's keep going. Come on.
Ooh.
I'm sure there's something going on.
Hey, you're so mad because you didn't just fail at work, right?
These are all fab!
Oh, you bought a lot!
Patcha.
Hey, Parn!
When did you get back?
I got back last night.
Oh, wait.
Look.
How's it? Pretty?
Superb!
My trip to Korea this time was superb!
I got a new nose and a new man.
That's fabulous.
Pat bought us loads of gifts.
These are all the popular facial masks.
- I'll put it on my face and all the way to-- - Stop!
Oops.
Pick some for yourself, Parn, or Miew will take everything.
- She's planning to put it on from her face to-- - Stop!
That's enough.
You guys take what you want. Just keep one for me.
Oh, sure, you're a saint.
Good, I'll use plenty of it,
so maybe this waitress could become the star of Paradise.
Whoa.
Come on, Parn was already pretty when she was washing dishes at the back.
Well, that's true.
Then, I'll go let others choose too, okay?
- Yeah. - Okay, I'll get going!
I felt so much happier washing dishes.
But you need money, don't you?
And now you can make much more money.
If I didn't have to send money to my family
and pay my father's debts,
I would still be washing dishes.
See? You're a great daughter. That's why you always get good things.
What good things?
Oh, you're being secretive, huh?
Miew already told me everything.
What did she tell you?
Well, a wealthy tycoon's heir was waiting around for you for two nights in a row.
What tycoon's heir?
Ms. Peem, of course!
You don't know who she is?
You know her?
Of course, I do.
Ms. Peem, Phakanee Traisuvetthiwat, is the daughter of Mr. Phakpoom,
the owner of a major shopping mall and one of the top three wealthiest figures in Asia.
She is incredibly wealthy and has a wonderful life.
She could die ten times and still have money left.
That figures.
What?
She's a brat, self-centered, and always uses money to solve problems.
Her mouth is as foul as a dog's.
It's nothing like when we were at the beach.
Huh?
Wait a sec. What beach?
You and Ms. Peem...
Oh, shit!
...have banged?!
And you just learned she's an escort?!
But you have a rule not to bang anyone?
You slept with her after knowing her for two days.
Do you have feelings for her?
You love her, right?
Hey, you totally surprised me, you know?
- How? - Hmm?
You never waited around for anyone.
I wasn't waiting around. I just wanted my work done.
If someone can help me seal the deal quickly, that's good, isn't it?
Oh, totally, nothing personal involved.
Hey.
That's the owner of the major transportation company
that’s reportedly closing the deal with the shopping app.
You whore!
Move!
You like to steal others' husbands, huh?
You're pretty.
And this is how you find a job?
I'll smash your face in!
This is a restaurant, ma'am. Please get out.
Let go of me!
You come here!
We need to go home and talk. Come here!
- Thank you. - Sure.
Why did you meddle in other people's business?
If a pretty face gets slapped, it'll be ruined.
Come on, I won't get slapped. Oh, oh, oh.
Oh my, you called me pretty.
You still haven't managed to make a deal with her?
Your Angel is playing hard to get.
I guess my offer wasn't enough.
Hey.
If you could buy her with money, you would've done it by now.
Tell me what the problem is.
I heard that Techin has managed to arrange a meeting with Mr. Songsak.
Isn't he abroad?
Do you know when the meeting is?
Next month, when he's back from Hongkong. I guess Techin arranged it then.
We're running out of time, Peem.
I won't charge you for today.
The work wasn't done, and you were humiliated too.
It's alright.
You...
Why are you surprised?
Did you forget I know where you live?
What are you doing here?
Come work for me.
I said no.
You're going to keep selling your body until you die?
I'm not selling it.
Then what was that today?
His wife asked for her husband back in front of everyone.
If you're not selling your body, what was that?
You don't like that I'm an escort,
but I also don't like that you look down on my job.
We should stop seeing each other and end this.
A whore like you has no right to order me around.
I am self-centered.
I get what I want.
And no one can say no to me.
You can't answer until we're done talking.
What did you say?
I'm on my way.
Where are you running to?
Please drive. I'll send you the location.
Where's Mamiew?
There.
Open! Open the door now!
Hey!
What's your problem?
Miew.
Parn, help me.
You sure you wanna do this?
I called the police.
Are you going to wait to be arrested for assault and rape?
The evidence is right there on Miew's face. I'm the witness. You're going to jail.
Hey! Don't run away!
Ow.
- You're driving me insane. - Walk slowly.
- Can you be more gentle, Ton? - Ugh.
Ah!
- Ton! - Miew.
Shoot.
- Guys. - Where's the police?
Huh?
Ton!
You guys, run!
Come on, Miew.
Where are you going?
- Parn. No. - Run, Miew. Run.
- Parn! - You're a smart-ass, huh?
- Hey! - Help!
It's a problem between husband and wife. Don't butt in.
Peem.
(Pak Kret Police Station)
The incident took place at a drive-in motel.
What were you doing there?
Prostitution?
My friend almost got raped and came here to report it.
She didn't come here to let you interview her about her personal life.
I had to ask about your profession.
Judging by the way she’s dressed,
I'm sure my guess is right.
You’re selling, he’s buying, that's a fair trade-off.
Why are you reporting it?
Was it consensual but there's a problem later?
She got slapped, locked up, physically assaulted, and almost sexually assaulted.
Isn't any of that against the law?
She could be soliciting, but then claimed she was raped,
and came to report it for money.
It's possible.
He told me we're having dinner,
but then he took me to the motel.
I don't believe you.
With experience in your field of work,
you wouldn't fall for such a simple trick from a guy. It's impossible.
So you're not taking the report?
It's enough, Ms. Peem.
I don't want to be here anymore.
Why did you give in?
You three gave in, but I won't.
What more can we ask for?
We've been humiliated enough.
No one values ​​people who do the kind of work we do.
When they looked down on you, it's like they're looking down on me too.
Whatever people say, we have to defend our own dignity.
And this isn't just about you anymore.
It affects my dignity.
Dad, I need your help with something.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Oh.
Please. Please have a seat.
Please. Please.
Please.
I'm sorry about earlier.
There's a little mix-up in the communication.
What a complete 180.
Ton.
This case falls under physical assault.
Huh?
And clearly unlawful imprisonment.
Oh?
Ow.
It hurts so much, officer.
Ouch! My liver and spleen hurt.
Don't worry. We'll do our best.
I'll contact the patrol team to check the surveillance footage at every location.
We'll find the perpetrator as soon as possible.
That’s good. Just follow the legal procedure.
I'll prepare the records
and contact the hospital to have the victims attend medical examinations.
Let's go home, then?
Are you sure you don't need a ride?
Oh.
It's alright. We can go on our own.
Thank you so much, Ms. Peem.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
You come with me.
Why are you standing? Sit down.
Who would dare to sit?
Oh?
Are you hurt?
Do you want me to treat your wound?
You're the one who got hurt.
Think about yourself too before you do anything.
Ow.
It hurts, right?
No.
You're so small. How could you stand a chance against him?
If I hadn't followed you, he would have got you and your friends.
I thought you got mad and went home.
I didn't expect you to follow.
I just wanted to know who you're going to fuck.
It's done.
Thank you.
Thank you isn't enough.
Then what do you want me to do?
Come work for me
to repay me for helping you and your friends today.
You won't be doing it for free. I'll pay you.
How much do you charge?
How much do you normally charge?
Three million.
If you don't dare to pay that amount,
please stop asking.
If I pay you that,
what can you do for me?
Here we go
Once again
Four hail Marys
Nine amen
Don’t you worry
It’s gonna be alright
‘Cause I’m the judge and jury
And we be up all night
You better check for pulse
Someone like me probably isn't a good fit to work for you.
We both said some awful words
And I know that we both got hurt
But I wanna be with you
I wanna be with you
We can't let this slip away
You know that I want you to stay
'Cause I wanna be with you
I wanna be with you
Don't run away
Do what you used to do.
But only do it with me.
Don't let this go to waste
Baby, we can work it out
Maybe you can stay the night
I wanna be with you
Spread your legs.
I just wanna let you know
I wanna be with you
You
I hope that we can work it out
But I know that you have your doubts
I wanna be with you
Don't you wanna be with me?
Turn around.
And I just want you here with me
I wanna be with you
You know it is the truth
Don't run away
We can't let this go to waste
I don't want nobody else, else
Don't let this go to waste
Baby, we can work it out
Maybe you can stay the night
I wanna be with you I wanna be with you
Stay with me here tonight.
I don't wanna let you go I just wanna let you know
I wanna be with you
Don't let this go to waste
Baby, we can work it out
Maybe you can stay the night
I wanna be with you
Don't let this go to waste
I don't wanna let you go
I just wanna let you know
I wanna be with you
I hope that we can work it out
Wanna feel you close to me
Parn.
She's gone again?
Oh, you're up?
Where were you rushing to that morning at the beach?
It's a personal matter.
What is it?
It's personal.
Are you seeing anyone?
Seeing who?
Lover? Partner? Husband?
I don't know what you call them. The one you're rushing to that day.
Think whatever you like.
I don't need to explain everything to everyone.
But I'm not everyone.
Sit.
I won't.
You're paying me millions to work for you
because you want to control my life, don't you?
I haven't agreed to work for you yet,
so my life is still mine.
You can't tell me to do whatever you want.
And I'm not taking your three million.
Where is it?
Where did I put it?
Ugh!
Why did I forget and leave it there?
(Mom)
Ms. Peem left it for you
and asked me to let you know that your mother had called, Ms. Parn.
Mom, you called me?
Yes.
Ms. Peem.
Please have some longan.
Thank you.
Oh, you're here?
What are you doing here?
Parn, be nice to your friend.
She came all the way here to see you.
It's alright, Dad.
Can you answer me?
What are you doing here?
She's here to help.
She's here to help clear all of our family's debts.
What debts now?
I just paid all the debts the other day.
There's one more.
How many people do you owe money to?
Calm down, Parn.
It's no big deal.
Let's talk outside.
You have no right to meddle with my family.
And what right do you have to tell me not to control your life?
That has nothing to do with this.
It does.
You want to help your family, right?
I can help you.
You don't even have to go back to selling your body.
How many more times do I have to say it? I don't sell my body.
Stop denying it.
I'm just giving you an option.
You're buying me.
I'm inviting you to work for me.
For you alone?
Yes.
Then I'm not doing it.
And stop using my family as leverage.
Then give me back my money.
Transfer back the money I paid to settle your father's debt.
It's five million. Do you have it, Parn?
If you don't have it,
use your body and work to pay off your debt.
While working for me,
you're not allowed to accept any other job or client.
And you're not allowed to fuck anyone else.
You have no right to use my things to make a living.
Your body belongs to me.
And you're not allowed to fuck anyone else without my permission.
Go buy some food to treat her.
Hey, where's Ms. Peem?
She left.
What?
I was about to go out to buy something to cook for her.
She won't eat our food, Mom.
Why?
What's wrong with our family?
You’re the only one who hates it.
I don't hate our family.
You don't hate our family,
but you're ashamed of it, so you left home to live alone at your condo.
So when you take your clients home, they won't know your family is poor.
And you said you don't hate it.
Honey.
But this one is good. Hold on to her tightly,
so we can stop being poor.
Huh? Quit?
Are you delirious from a fever?
Can you tell Sis Mol for me?
What? Why don't you go tell her yourself?
I don't dare to.
I'm afraid I won't be able to say it.
If you leave this place, she'll be in trouble.
Everyone came because of you, Parn.
How much did she pay you to get you to do this?
Whatever.
I'm leaving. Just tell her for me.
Wait, Parn.
- Hello? - Did you quit your job yet?
Pardon?
Why didn't you answer my call?
Is your work for the final night not finished yet?
How did you get my number?
Did you forget you left your phone at my place?
This is my number. Save it.
And get ready. I'm on my way to pick you up.
I'll buy everything that looks good on her.
Hey, it's 150,000.
If I wear this, I think I'll be able to fly.
It's my money, not yours.
Try it on.
Okay.
Good.
This is also good.
So people stop looking at you the same way.
I'll take all.
One is enough.
It's too expensive.
From now on, there's nothing too expensive.
Because you're not the same cheap woman.
How many good outfits do you have?
I bought them because I want you to look clean when you meet my business partners.
I just think it's a waste of money.
It's not a waste to me.
(Mr. Techin)
I'll keep it brief.
Don't call Parn again.
You can't do that.
I can. I just did. Didn't you see?
And if a guy calls you again, I'll do it again.
Don't forget I spent millions to buy you.
If you want to fuck someone,
hold back for now.
Is my work done here?
If it's done, I'll go home.
Take them with you.
I'll only take what I'll use.
What kind of person is she?
She's hot and then she's cold.
(Techin)
Mr. Techin.
I spent millions to buy you.
If you want to fuck someone,
hold back for now.
(Didn't you say you made a deal with her?)
(Why did someone see her with Techin?)
You're so quick to leave
because you're going to meet Techin?
You can change your clothes,
but you can't change the slut that you are, huh?!
Let go of me.
What I do is none of your business.
You're just my boss. You don't own my life.
Ms. Peem!
Whatever you do, wherever you go, and whoever you go with, you must report to me.
Because you belong to me. Do you understand?!
Ms. Peem, stop it!
Don't do this to me!
Ms. Peem!
Remember this.
You are mine, and mine alone!
Do you understand?
Let go.
Hands that reach but never touch me
Eyes that plead through the screen
Dance for me my pixelated dream
Eyes so big and hungry
Broken apart, how you found me
Longing virtually
Meet me at the building at nine.
And if you manage to close the deal for me,
I’ll give you another five million,
and wipe out your family's five-million-baht debt.
Good luck.
Take the contract along with Angel.
I already told Mr. Songsak.
You look pretty now.
Paradise Club's Angel is even prettier than what they say.
You know what I want now, right?
♪Even though my heart says I love you♪
♪Why am I like this?♪
♪I don't understand♪
♪What's wrong with my mouth and my heart?♪